pandonetworks.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - Reloaded Technologies, Inc.

**July 31, 2013**

**OVERVIEW**

Reloaded Technologies, Inc. ("RTI ") recognizes that privacy is important. This document ("Privacy Policy") outlines the types of information we gather when you use RTI's download manager and other software ("Software") to download content distributed through RTI's content delivery network ("Network"). By using the Software, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Software or access our service.

**INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

RTI **does not** collect personally identifying information when you use our products and services. RTI offers content delivery services that do not require you to register or provide any personal information to us. However, in order to operate our Network we may collect the following types of information:

> **Log information -** When you use the Software to download a file published into our Network by one of our media customers, our servers automatically record information that pertains to your file transfer. These logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your transfer as well as reports on the progress and completion of the file transfer.
> 
> **Crash Reports -** A sample of crashes in the Software may be reported to an automatic analysis system. These reports are then analyzed by our engineers and issues are fixed in future versions of the software. These reports help us to maintain and improve the quality of our products and services.
> 
> **User communications -** When you send email or other communications to RTI, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
> 
> **Advertisers -** We may allow advertisers, third party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies and other companies to serve or enable other sites to serve advertisements directly to you, and/or enable other services through the use of RTI's (and affiliates) websites, services, and Software. By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer and trigger their own Web beacons.
> 
> **Other sites -** This Privacy Policy applies to RTI's Software and services only. We do not exercise control over the sites that use our products or services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

**SECURITY**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

**CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our website. All amended terms shall automatically be effective immediately. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**ENFORCEMENT**

RTI regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting us at [policies@reloadedtech.com](mailto:policies@reloadedtech.com).
